Federal Subcontracts, 1966-1979
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Federal Subcontracts
1966-1979
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory, Subcontracts and Procurement Department
SI Records
16 cu. ft. (16 record storage boxes)
Accession 99-080
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of records that document Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (SAO) projects and activities. Materials include proposals, quotations, bids, and correspondence with contractors, equipment makers, and vendors to provide services, equipments, and instruments for SAO.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Subject
Astrophysical observatories.
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Manuscripts
- Box 1
  - SFC-7-0005: Evans and Joplins, August 1966 (Box 1 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0006: Metcalf and Eddy, Inc., October 1966 (Box 1 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0007: Optics for Industry, November 1966 (Box 1 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0008: Metcalf and Eddy, Inc., April 1967 (Box 1 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0009: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co. Inc., December 1966 (Box 1 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0095: Boiler and Chivens, March 1967 (Box 1 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0096: Scientific-Atlanta, March 1967 (Box 1 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0097: Smithsonian Research Foundation, March 1967 (Box 1 of 16)
- Box 2
  - SFC-7-0098: Blanton Co., May 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0099: New England Steel Tank Co., June 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0151: RF Systems, Inc., June 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0152: RF Systems, Inc., June 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0153: New England Steel Tank Co., June 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0154: Blanton Co., June 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-7-0155: Good Construction, August 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-8-1506: William J. Davis, July 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7101: Materials Analysis Co., September 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7102: Simpson, Gumpertz, Heger, Inc., November 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7103: Lynch Engineering Construction Co., September 1967 (Box 2 of 16)
- Box 3
  - SFC-8-7103: Lynch Engineering Construction Co., September 1967 (continued) (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7104: Mountain State Telephone Telegraph, Cancelled (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7105: Smithsonian Research Foundation, December 1967 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7106: Kinney Vacuum, November 1969 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7107: Rohr Corporation, March 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7108: Ludium Measurements, Inc., March 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7109: Raytheon, May 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7110: Mr. Thomas C. Marvin, May 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7111: Owens-Illinois, Inc., June 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7112: Burr-Brown Research Corporation, June 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-8-7113: Hewlett Packard, June 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9001: Blanton Co., November 1968 (Box 3 of 16)
- Box 4
  - SFC-9-9001: Blanton Co., November 1968 (continued) (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9002: Smithsonian Research Foundation, December 1968 (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9003: Wang Laboratories, Filed elsewhere (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9004: Boydon Observatory, Filed elsewhere (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9005: Phototechnical Research Institute, March 1969 (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9006: National Academy of Sciences, March 1969 (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9007: RF Systems, Inc., March 1969 (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9008: Wang Laboratories, Filed elsewhere (Box 4 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9009: Tinsley Laboratories, May 1969 (Box 4 of 16)
- Box 5
  - SFC-9-9010: RF Systems, Inc., May 1969 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9011: Airborne Instruments Laboratory, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9012: Tobe Deutschman Co., Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9013: Harvard College Observatory Model Shop, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9014: Harvard College Observatory Model Shop, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-9-9015: Harvard College Observatory Model Shop, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9001: Observa-Dome Laboratories, September 1969 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9002: George C. Codd Construction Co., July 1969 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9003: Boyden Observatory, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9004: RF Systems, Inc., March 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9005: Simpson, Gumpertz, Heger, Inc., June 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9006: Tektronix, June 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9007: Picker Corporation, June 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9008: Varian, June 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9009: Digi-Data Corporation, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9010: Lico Inc., Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9011: Hewlett Packard, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9012: Pitney Bowes, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9013: Hewlett Packard, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-0-9014: Wang Laboratories, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9100: Digi-Data Corporation, August 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9101: Cober Electronics, September 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9102: Boyden Observatory, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9103: AGA Corporation, Filed elsewhere (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9104: Infrared Labs, Inc., October 1970 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9105: Optics for Industry, January 1971 (Box 5 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9106: Cella, Bar, Evans Associates, March 1971 (Box 5 of 16)
- Box 6
  - SFC-1-9107: President and Fellows of Harvard College, April 1971 (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9108: Radio Research Instrument Co., March 1971 (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9109: Ortec Inc., June 1971 (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9110: Materials Analysis Co., June 1971 (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-1-9111: SSR Instruments Co., June 1971 (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9902: Massachusetts Institute of Technology, December 1971 (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9903: Blanton Co., December 1971 (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9904: Smithsonian Institution, Not Issued (Box 6 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9905: University of Arizona, May 1972 (Box 6 of 16)
- Box 7
  - SFC-2-9005: University of Arizona, May 1972 (continued) (Box 7 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9906: Liberty Mirror, March 1972 (Box 7 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9907: Varian Associates of Canada, Ltd., March 1972 (Box 7 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9908: Sierrita Mining Ranching Co., Inc., May 1972 (Box 7 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9909: Varian Associates of Canada, Ltd., May 1972 (Box 7 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9910: Philco-Ford Corporation., June 1972 (Box 7 of 16)
- Box 8
  - SFC-2-9910: Philco-Ford Corporation, June 1972 (continued) (Box 8 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9911: Cyclone Fence - U.S. Steel Corporation, June 1972 (Box 8 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9912: Princeton Applied Research Corporation, June 1972 (Box 8 of 16)
  - SFC-2-9913: RF Systems, Inc., June 1972 (Box 8 of 16)
  - FC-3-93001: Simpson, Gumpertz Heger, Inc., October 1972 (Box 8 of 16)
- Box 9
  - FC-3-93002: Steel-Fab Inc., September 1972 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93003: Department of the Army - Corporation of Army Engineers, October 1972 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93004: Cella, Bar, Evans Associates, January 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93005: Cella, Bar, Evans Associates, December 1972 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93006: Cella, Bar, Evans Associates, January 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93007: Cambridge Circuit Company, March 1972 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93008: Varian Associates of Canada Ltd., February 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93009: Data General Corporation, April 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93010: Caterpillar Tractor Co., June 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93011: Garland Steel Co., June 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93012: Wallace, Floyd, Ellenzweig Inc., June 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
  - FC-3-93013: Varian Associates of Canada, June 1973 (Box 9 of 16)
- Box 10
  - FC-3-93014: Data General Corp., June 1973 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-3-93015: PRO Electonics Inc., June 1973 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-3-93016: Owens-Illinois, Inc., June 1973 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15001: Boyden Observatory (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15002: Department of the Army - Corporation of Army Engineers, August 1973 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15003: Harvard College Observatory (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15004: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co., Inc., October 1973 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15005: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co., Inc., November 1973 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15006: Cella, Bar, Evans and Associates, November 1973 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15007: Cella, Bar, Evans and Associates, January 1974 (Box 10 of 16)
  - FC-4-15008: Wallace, Floyd, Ellenzweig, Inc., March 1974 (Box 10 of 16)
- Box 11
  - FC-4-15008: Wallace, Floyd, Ellenzweig, Inc., March 1974 (continued) (Box 11 of 16)
  - FC-4-15009: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co., Inc., February 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - FC-4-15010: Owens-Illinois, Inc., April 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - FC-4-15011: Lang Construction Systems, May 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - FC-4-15012: Datalight Inc., June 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - FC-4-15013: Reticon Corporation, June 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - FC-4-15014: Kilovolt Corporation, June 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - SFC-5-9000: Philco-Ford Corporation, September 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - SFC-5-9002: Citizens Utility Company, September 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
  - SFC-5-9003: Philco-Ford Corporation, September 1974 (Box 11 of 16)
- Box 12
  - SFC-5-9003: Philco-Ford Corporation, September 1974 (continued) (Box 12 of 16)
  - SFC-5-9004: Simpson, Gumpertz, Heger, Inc., October 1974 (Box 12 of 16)
  - SFC-5-9005: Sierrita Mining Ranching Co., Inc., March 1975 (Box 12 of 16)
  - SFC-5-9006: Aeronautronic Ford Corporation, April 1975 (Box 12 of 16)
- Box 13
  - SFC-5-9006: Aeronautronic Ford Corporation, April 1975 (continued) (Box 13 of 16)
- Box 14
  - SFC-5-9006: Aeronautronic Ford Corporation, April 1975 (continued) (Box 14 of 16)
  - SFC-5-9007: Micromega Division/Bunker Ramo Corporation, June 1976 (Box 14 of 16)
  - SK6-09000: Sierrita Mining Ranching Co., Inc., June 1976 (Box 14 of 16)
  - SK7-60001: National Science Foundation, November 1976 (Box 14 of 16)
  - SK7-60002: The Excalibur Corporation, January 1977 (Box 14 of 16)
  - SK7-60003: Votaw Precision Tool Co., February 1977 (Box 14 of 16)
  - SK7-60004: Raytheon Co., February 1977 (Box 14 of 16)
  - SK7-60005: Batson-Stark Electrical Contractors, May 1977 (Box 14 of 16)
  - SK7-60006: Pace Construction Co., June 1977 (Box 14 of 16)
- Box 15
  - SK7-60007: Equipment Sales Company, August 1977 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK7-60008: Varian Associates, Inc., September 1977 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK7-60009: Raytheon Company, September 1977 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK8-60001: Cimetta Engineering and Construction Co., Inc., June 1978 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK8-60002: Blanton and Company, June 1978 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK8-60003: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co., Inc., July 1978 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK8-60004: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co., Inc., August 1978 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK8-60005: Reticon Coporation, September 1978 (Box 15 of 16)
  - SK8-60006: Pace Construction Company, March 1978 (Box 15 of 16)
- Box 16
  - SK8-60007: Digital Equipment Corporation, September 1978 (Box 16 of 16)
  - SK9-60001: University of Arizona, October 1978 (Box 16 of 16)
  - SK9-60002: Itek Corporation, February 1979 (Box 16 of 16)
  - SK9-60003: University of Arizona, March 1979 (Box 16 of 16)
  - SK9-60004: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co., Inc., March 1979 (Box 16 of 16)
  - SK9-60005: Sierrita Mining and Ranching Co., Inc., March 1979 (Box 16 of 16)
  - SK9-60006: Dr. Douglas E. Kleinmann, June 1979 (Box 16 of 16)